connecticutbloggers.com 2012-05-28

# Privacy Policy and Disclosure Policies

**Privacy Policy** **and Disclosure Statements**

_These policies are valid from January 23, 2012._

Connecticut Bloggers is a blog written and edited by Wendy Limauge, Greg Limauge and guest writers. We may receive products directly from brands, manufacturers, public relations companies, and brand marketing firms. In addition we have be invited to fairs, shows, and other events. Complimentary services, gratis products, tickets and press samples never compromise our coverage of the product or event. We will always cover whatever we receive fairly and honestly..

Connecticut Bloggers will not be paid for a review but may receive complimentary products, services, tickets, and travel in exchange for our opinion. Any advice on this site is the opinion of Connecticut Bloggers, and any/all contributing editors for this site. We are in no way responsible for the effects of our advice and always suggest that our readers decide for themselves.

If there are any images listed on this site you would like removed, please **email us** and they will be removed promptly.

**Commitment to Online Security**

Personal information submitted to Connecticut Bloggers is only accessible only the owner of this site.

**Personal Information Collected by** **Connecticut Bloggers**  
Connecticut Bloggers may ask you to provide the following types of personal information: name, postal address, email addresses, and phone numbers. This information is given freely by you and is not required to view, read, or use this site. Connecticut Bloggers may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information such as the date of your visit to the site, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP, Mac OS, etc.), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Comcast, etc.), and the IP Address of your computer.

Connecticut Bloggers does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 18 without the expressed permission from a parent or legal guardian, and the site is not structured to attract anyone under the age of 18.

**How Connecticut Bloggers** **Uses Personal Information Collected Online**  
Connecticut Bloggers will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries and comments, provide operational notices, publish a newsletter, and program or sweepstakes participation. By completing an entry or registration form you are allowing us store your information in a database for retrieval at a future time for purposes of picking a winner for a giveaway or contacting you with site updates.

Connecticut Bloggers will never sell, rent or share your personal information with third-parties.

In general, you are responsible for the information you submit in the form of a comment on a post on this blog. Your comments can be read by anyone and your profile can be viewed by anyone. You are allowed to post as an Anonymous reader as a way to help protect your privacy. This blog uses Google Docs forms for some of it’s giveaways in order to collect information from readers.

**Materials Submitted to Connecticut Bloggers**  
All photos, written correspondence and any other materials submitted to Connecticut Bloggers become the sole and exclusive property of Connecticut Bloggers and cannot be returned at any time. By submitting Materials, you agree that Connecticut Bloggers may, but is not obligated to, use the Materials in connection with the site, in any way, in any medium, worldwide, in perpetuity. Further, you warrant all Materials are 100% original and do not violate the right of privacy or publicity of, or constitute a defamation against, any person or entity; that the Materials will not infringe upon or violate the copyright or common law rights or any other rights of any person or entity; that there are and will be no encumbrances, liens, conditions or restrictions whatsoever upon or affecting such Materials; and that you and the person depicted in the Materials are at least 18 years of age or you are a parent or guardian granting permission for use. You agree to indemnify Connecticut Bloggers for all damages and expenses (including reasonable attorney’s fees) arising out of any breach or failure of the warranties made herein.

**Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate**  
If your personal information changes please submit the changes to Connecticut Bloggers by email at info@connecticutbloggers.com. Please be sure to note that you are “updating” your information.

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**  
Our site is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. Our website also recognizes the online site where a visitor clicked one of our banners or buttons to follow through and visit our site, but we cannot identify the visitor or the visitor’s address. Site information is used to confirm promotion of Connecticut Bloggers giveaways, newsletter, or other projects, and may be used to advise participants of the numbers of visitors who come to our site from their sites.

**Third Party Ads**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Disclaimer Policy**  
This blog will contain links to other websites and blogs. All external links contain content which is not endorsed or controlled by this blog. All information that you submit on other websites is done so at your own risk. If you are concerned about the sites you visit from this please read the “Privacy Policy” of each website or blog you visit. Your feedback and assistance is welcome in updating the information on this site if you find updates or errors.

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url [ www.google.com/privacy_ads](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Connecticut Bloggers has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Connecticut Bloggers, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Connecticut Bloggers has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

The ads you see on Connecticut Bloggers may be affiliate accounts for products that may be of interested to readers of this site. We may receive products or monetary compensation for recommendations made in reference to the products/ services on this website. Most ads posted are typically chosen because it’s a product we have tried and approve of.

This disclosure is made in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s 16 CFR, Part 255: “Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising.”

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Connecticut Bloggers then you may contact us at info@connecticutbloggers.com
